{
    "id": "14a1941887d94b4eba361436077890cc",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ..................... . up several times in the night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "woke",
                "have waken",
                "had woken"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My mother ....................... delicious meals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cook",
                "cooks",
                "have cooked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She .....................… the answer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not knows",
                "do not know",
                "does not know"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys ....................... in the garden when it started raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are playing",
                "were playing",
                "played"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... .. for him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "am waiting",
                "have waited"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I …..................... . the parcel yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "receive",
                "had received",
                "received"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I .....................…… that movie three times.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watched",
                "have watched",
                "had watched"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Goats and cows .....................… us milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gives",
                "give",
                "gave"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Cows ..................... .. on grass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "feeds",
                "feed",
                "fed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I …..................... . for his call since yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "waited",
                "am waiting",
                "have been waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I .....................…… all the books written by Dickens.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "am reading",
                "have read"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ...................... in two films.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "acted",
                "has acted",
                "acts"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ....................... nice portraits.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "draw",
                "draws",
                "has drawn"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}